yoursearch.me 2017-02-26

# FVD Speed Dial - Privacy Policy

This pages lists the types of information that we collect from our users and shows what exactly we use that information for. We want to make sure you are aware of it so that you always see the whole picture of your interaction with us. Please, read this Privacy Policy in full as by installing our add-on or visiting our website you express your acceptance of the practices we list here. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, don’t hesitate to contact our Support service. The definitions of the terms that are shown capitalized on this page are available from our Terms of Service.

## What types of information does FVD Speed Dial collect?

1)FVD Speed Dial collects the information that you provide when getting registered at our site (your email address and password) 

2) Every time you use the Sync feature in our addons FVD Speed Dial or Eversync (automatically or in manual mode), our servers collect and save the following information: 

  * a) FVD Speed Dial structure 
  * b) FVD Speed Dial groups 
  * c) FVD Speed Dial dials 
  * d) Screenshots of all dials 

## How does FVD Speed Dial use the information collected during syncing?

1) The information provided by you during the registration is used for creating an account at our synchronization server and giving you the access to it. 

2) The information from your FVD Speed Dial is saved on the server and used for data backup and further syncing with other computers. 

You can sync the speed dials for use on different computers in automatic or manual modes. Automatic syncing can be deactivated in add-on settings.

## How do you protect my personal information?

FVD Speed Dial takes all measures required to keep your information safe. We take this matter very seriously and always do our best to live up to our customers’ security expectations.   
We want to ask you to collaborate with us as the precautions you yourself take also play a significant role in your security at FVD Speed Dial. Just follow our simple tips here – don’t share your access detail from FVD Speed Dial with anyone and remember to change them frequently. This helps prevent your personal information from unauthorized access by third parties.   
Please, log out of FVD Speed Dial every time you are done using our product. If possible, also exit your browser so that no people with access to your computer can use our site with your username and password.   
Planning to sell your computer or to give it to another person for an extended period of time? Please, don’t forget to uninstall FVD Speed Dial Add-on before you do that.

## Is there a chance FVD Speed Dial could make my personal information or content publicly available?

No. Nevertheless, you should remember about the "public" sections of the FVD Speed Dial service and websites - such as FVD Speed Dial message board or user notebooks, for instance. Such sections can be viewed by any user on the Internet. Please, note that you should avoid sharing your contacts or other personal information in such sections of the websites or service if you want to protect yourself from unsolicited messages. Hereby Everhelper disclaims all responsibility for publication and use of the personal information that has been posted in public sections of FVD Speed Dial by you.

Extension uses Google Analytics and cookies for internal use. We track performance to understand which way is better to develop product. We don't share data to any third-party services. 

## In-app ads

Quick Preview widget 

For some websites (like Amazon for example), Quick Preview widget shows additional information, such as product details and its price, if a link to Amazon is present. In some cases (Amazon can still be used as an example), an affiliate ID - couponpartnerfvd or param_fvd-20 - would be added to the link when getting transferred to the site. The link on speed-dials still remains unchanged, just the way the user created it. 

Default dials 

When the app is installed, a few default speed dials are added. Some of those (for instance, Amazon, Booking etc.) would contain the affiliate ID in the link. Default speed dials are in no way different from regular ones, so users can delete or change them without the efficiency of the app affected in any way.
